<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Albums on ProjectName</title>
    <link>https://www.marinart.de/albums/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Albums on ProjectName</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.marinart.de/albums/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Provence</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/albums/provence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/albums/provence/</guid>
      <description>Manosque, vue de la chapelle Saint-Pancrace, de Toutes Aures 2021. Oil on canvas. 50x30 Montfuron, vue de moulin à vent 2021. Oil on canvas. 50x40 Manosque, mont d’Or et les pies dans le champ 2021. Watercolor on paper. 30x20 View of Mont d’Or 2021. Oil on canvas. 50x40 Manosque on a hot day 2021. Oil on canvas. 50x30 Manosque, porte de Soubeyran du XIV siècle 2021. Oil on canvas. 50x40 Manosque, une demi-heure avant le couvre-feu 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Munich</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/albums/munich/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/albums/munich/</guid>
      <description>In the old parc 2020. Oil on carton. 26x24 On the Isar 2020. Oil on carton. 26x19 Im Englischen Garten 2020. Oil on carton. 27x27 Bridge over the Isar 2020. Oil on carton. 32x19 Bell tower of the Josephskirche 2020. Oil on carton. 18x32 Nymphenburger сhannel 2020. Oil on carton. 34x19 In the rythm of 2&amp;#43;2&amp;#43; 2020. Watercolor on paper. 23x30 Siegestor in winter 2020. Watercolor on paper. 34x52 Siegestor at night 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acryl and ink</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/albums/acryl-ink/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/albums/acryl-ink/</guid>
      <description>The descended angel 2016. Acryl/ink on paper. a5 The descended angel 2016. Acryl/ink on paper. Fragment The descended angel 2016. Acryl/ink on paper. Fragment The descended angel 2016. Acryl/ink on paper. Fragment Tree on the slope 2016. Acryl/ink on paper. a5 Boat in a storm 2016. Acryl/ink on paper. a5 Colored tree 2016. Acryl/ink on paper. a5 Colored tree 2016. Acryl/ink on paper. Fragment The little bear 2016. Acryl/ink on paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automn serie</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/albums/automn-serie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/albums/automn-serie/</guid>
      <description>Automn series 2016. Watercolor on paper. a5 Automn series 2016. Watercolor on paper. a5 Automn series 2016. Watercolor on paper. a5 Automn series 2016. Watercolor on paper. a5 Automn series 2016. Watercolor on paper. a5 Automn series 2016. Watercolor on paper. a5 Automn series 2016. Watercolor on paper. a5 Automn series 2016. Watercolor on paper. a5 Automn series 2016. Watercolor on paper. a5 Automn series 2016. Watercolor on paper. a5 Automn series 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Composition</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/albums/composition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/albums/composition/</guid>
      <description>Dolphins in Venice 2020. Watercolor on paper. 38x56 Dance of Demeter 2020. Oil on canvas. 120x80 Dance of Demeter 2020. Oil on canvas. Fragment Red sunflower 2017. Mixed technique, canvas. 80x60 Annunciation of Mary 2015. Oil on canvas. 80x120 Annunciation of Mary 2015. Oil on canvas. Fragment Annunciation of Mary 2015. Oil on canvas. Fragment Annunciation of Mary 2015. Oil on canvas. Fragment Annunciation of Mary 2015. Oil on canvas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Still life</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/albums/still-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/albums/still-life/</guid>
      <description>Portuguese roses 2021. Acryl on canvas. 30x30 Old coffe machine 2018. Oil on canvas. 60x40 Bunch of roses 2017. Oil on canvas. 40x40 Cyclamen 2015. Oil on canvas. 50x70 Magnolia 2015. Oil on canvas. 50x70 Shapdragon 2015. Oil on canvas. 50x70 Roosters and Pumpkins 2013. Oil on canvas. 80x40 Rhino and Rose 2013. Oil on canvas. 80x60 Apples and chestnuts 2012. Oil on canvas. 60x30 Sunflowers 2012. Oil on canvas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Otranto, Italy</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/albums/otranto/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/albums/otranto/</guid>
      <description> Otranto. Italy 2016. Watercolor on paper. 50x40 Otranto Bay 2016. Watercolor on paper. 50x40 Otranto Beach 2016. Watercolor on paper. 50x40 Otranto Cactus 2016. Watercolor on paper. 50x40 Otranto Harbor 2016. Watercolor on paper. 50x40 Otranto Villa 2016. Watercolor on paper. 50x40 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portrait</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/albums/portrait/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/albums/portrait/</guid>
      <description>Heraklius from Greece 2020. Sauce on paper. 40x50 Lets play in the snow! 2020. Watercolor on paper. 31x41 Snezhana 2020. Oil on canvas. 30x40 Robert 2020. Oil on canvas. 40x60 Transformation. Portrait of a daughter. 2020. Pencil on paper. a4 Heraclius from Greece 2020. Watercolor on paper. 23x31 Girl in orange 2020. Oil on canvas. 50x50 The girl on a stone. Tribute to Picasso. 2020. Watercolor on paper. 37x55 Daniel Mendelson 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Landscape</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/albums/landscape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/albums/landscape/</guid>
      <description>Paris, scene in subway 2020. Watercolor on paper. 38x56 Paris, Jardin du Luxembourg 2020. Watercolor on paper. 31x23 Paris, sunday morning 2020. Watercolor on paper. 23x31 Paris, view of Petit Pont 2020. Watercolor on paper. 31x23 Paris, spring is coming 2020. Watercolor on paper. 41x31 Loket, Czech 2019. Oil on canvas. 70x50 Loket, Czech 2019. Oil on canvas. 40x40 Loket, Czech 2019. Oil on canvas. 40x40 Loket, Czech 2019. Pencil on paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mediterranean</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/albums/mediterranean/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/albums/mediterranean/</guid>
      <description>Imperia, Liguria in September 2014. Oil on canvas. 60x40 Colle dei Bardellini in Imperia 2014. Oil on canvas. 40x40 La Côte Bleue 2014. Oil on canvas. 40x40 View of Marseille 2014. Oil on canvas. 60x30 Sardegna, Vignola bay 2012. Oil on canvas. 50x40 Sardegna, Vignola, beach 2012. Oil on canvas. 40x30 Sardegna, Vignola, sailing boats 2012. Oil on canvas. 30x40 Sardegna, Vignola, Palme 2012. Oil on canvas. 50x40 Sardegna, St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Water color nature</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/albums/water-color-nature/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/albums/water-color-nature/</guid>
      <description>Angry cat 2021. Watercolor on paper. 31x23 Koala 2021. Watercolor on paper. 23x31 Black kitten 2021. Watercolor on paper. 31x23 Young fox 2020. Watercolor on paper. 23x31 Elephant in blue weightlessness (jodymacdonaldphotography) 2019. Watercolor on paper. 50x40 Lionesse 2019. Watercolor on paper. 30x40 Sad dog 2019. Watercolor on paper. 50x40 Burro in spring 2019. Watercolor on paper. 32x24 Deer 2018. Watercolor on paper. 30x30 Blue cat 2018. Watercolor on paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acryl flowers</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/albums/acryl-flowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/albums/acryl-flowers/</guid>
      <description>Acryl flowers 2017. Acryl on paper. a4 Acryl flowers 2017. Acryl on paper. a4 Acryl flowers 2017. Acryl on paper. a4 Acryl flowers 2017. Acryl on paper. a4 Acryl flowers 2017. Acryl on paper. a4 Acryl flowers 2017. Acryl on paper. a4 Acryl flowers 2017. Acryl on paper. a4 Acryl flowers 2017. Acryl on paper. a4 Acryl flowers 2017. Acryl on paper. a4 Acryl flowers 2017. Acryl on paper. a4 Acryl flowers 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Model</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/albums/model/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/albums/model/</guid>
      <description>Model 2020. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2020. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2020. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2020. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2020. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2020. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2020. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2020. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2020. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2019. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2019. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2019. Pencil on paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Normandie</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/albums/normandie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/albums/normandie/</guid>
      <description>Deauville, parasoles 2018. Watercolor on paper. a5 Deauville, sunset 2018. Watercolor on paper. a5 Plein air in Etretat 2018. Watercolor on paper. 35x25 Etretat, sketch 2018. Ink/paper. a5 Etretat, sketch 2018. Ink/paper. a5 Etretat, sketch 2018. Ink/paper. a5 Deauville, in the harbor 2018. Watercolor on paper. 50x40 Fantasy flowers in Normandie 2018. Watercolor on paper. 25x35 Portrait of Normandie Girl 2018. Watercolor on paper. 25x35 Trouville-sur-Mer, the church 2018. Watercolor on paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illustrations</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/albums/illustration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/albums/illustration/</guid>
      <description> Goats, climbing on argan tree, Marokko 2019. Watercolor on paper. 56x38 In the library 2018. Watercolor on paper. 50x40 Old horse Lennon 2018. Watercolor on paper. 50x40 Baby elephant and ram 2018. Watercolor on paper. 40x50 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Altaj</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/albums/altaj/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/albums/altaj/</guid>
      <description>Katun River near the village of Aya, Altai mountains 2018. Watercolor on paper. 40x30 View on Katun river valley, Devil`s finger, Altai mountains 2018. Watercolor on paper. 40x30 Aktach, Altai mountains 2018. Watercolor on paper. 31x23 Aktach, Altai mountains 2018. Watercolor on paper. 31x23 Aktach, Altai mountains 2018. Watercolor on paper. 31x23 Road through the village Aktach, Altai mountains 2018. Watercolor on paper. 40x30 Glacier Aktru, Altai mountains 2018. Watercolor on paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Birds</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/albums/birds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/albums/birds/</guid>
      <description>Great tit (Parus major) 2018. Watercolor on paper. 15x19 Budgerigar (Melopsittacus undulatus) 2018. Watercolor on paper. 26x40 House sparrow (Passer domesticus) 2018. Watercolor on paper. 34x24 European robin (Erithacus rubecula) 2018. Watercolor on paper. 15x15 Common kingfisher (Alcedo atthis) 2018. Watercolor on paper. 15x19 Eurasian blue tit (Cyanistes caeruleus) 2018. Watercolor on paper. 18x14 Bohemian waxwing (Bombycilla garrulus) 2018. Watercolor on paper. 31x26 Bullfinch (Pyrrhula pyrrhula) 2018. Watercolor on paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rovinj, Croatia</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/albums/rovinj/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/albums/rovinj/</guid>
      <description>Rovinj, after the rain 2019. Watercolor on paper. 23x31 Rovinj, boats 2019. Watercolor on paper. 50x40 Rovinj, boats 2019. Watercolor on paper. Fragment Rovinj, boats 2019. Watercolor on paper. Fragment Rovinj, Eufemije church 2019. Watercolor on paper. 40x50 Rovinj, Eufemije church 2019. Watercolor on paper. Fragment Rovinj, Eufemije church 2019. Watercolor on paper. Fragment Rovinj, birds and clouds 2019. Watercolor on paper. 31x23 Rovinj 2019. Watercolor on paper. 31x23 Rovinj 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cologne</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/albums/cologne/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/albums/cologne/</guid>
      <description>Cologne Cathedral 2019. Watercolor on paper. 31x41 Cologne, city hall in the evening 2019. Watercolor on paper. 23x31 Cologne, St. Martin church in the evening 2019. Watercolor on paper. 23x31 Brühl, the castle Augustusburg 2019. Watercolor on paper. 41x31 Cologne, skecthes 2019. Ink/paper. 30x15 Cologne 2019. Watercolor on paper. 31x41 Cologne, bridge panorama 2019. Watercolor on paper. 40x30 Köln, Am Heumarkt, Reiterstandbild Friedrich Wilhelm III 2019. Watercolor on paper. 41x31 Cologne Cathedral 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Letters</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/albums/letters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/albums/letters/</guid>
      <description>Letter F 2019. Ink/paper. a4 Letter L 2019. Ink/paper. a4 Letter E 2019. Ink/paper. a4 Letter O 2019. Ink/paper. a4 Letter T 2019. Ink/paper. a4 Letter J 2020. Ink/paper. a4 Letter A 2020. Ink/paper. a4 Letter D 2020. Ink/paper. a4 Letter E 2020. Ink/paper. a4 Letter J 2020. Ink/paper. a4 Letter F 2020. Ink/paper. a4 Letter L 2020. Ink/paper. a4 Letter Z 2020. Ink/paper. a4 Letter M 2020. Ink/paper. a4 Letter N 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portugal</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/albums/portugal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/albums/portugal/</guid>
      <description>Dunes and ocean, Foz do Arelho 2020. Watercolor on paper. 31x23 Dunes and ocean, Foz do Arelho 2020. Watercolor on paper. Fragment Dunes and ocean, Foz do Arelho 2020. Watercolor on paper. Fragment Marina da Nazaré 2020. Watercolor on paper. 31x41 Marina da Nazaré 2020. Watercolor on paper. Fragment Capela da Santa Ana, Sao Martinho do Porto 2020. Sepia/paper. a4 Capela da Santa Ana, Sao Martinho do Porto 2020. Sepia/paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inktober</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/albums/inktober/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/albums/inktober/</guid>
      <description>Fish. Inktober 2020. Day 1. 2020. Ink/paper. a4 Wisp. Inktober 2020. Day 2. 2020. Ink/paper. a4 Bulky. Inktober 2020. Day 3. 2020. Ink/paper. a4 Radio. Inktober 2020. Day 4. 2020. Ink/paper. a4 Blade. Inktober 2020. Day 5. 2020. Ink/paper. a4 Rodent. Inktober 2020. Day 6. 2020. Ink/paper. a4 Fancy. Inktober 2020. Day 7. 2020. Ink/paper. a4 Teeth. Inktober 2020. Day 8. 2020. Ink/paper. a4 Throw. Inktober 2020. Day 9. 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
