<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pencil-on-paper on ProjectName</title>
    <link>https://www.marinart.de/tags/pencil-on-paper/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pencil-on-paper on ProjectName</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.marinart.de/tags/pencil-on-paper/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Transformation. Portrait of a daughter.</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/journal/post-2020-09-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/journal/post-2020-09-15/</guid>
      <description> Transformation. Portrait of a daughter. 2020. Pencil on paper. a4 Transformation. Portrait of a daughter. 2020. Pencil on paper. a4 Transformation. Portrait of a daughter. 2020. Pencil on paper. a4 Transformation. Portrait of a daughter. 2020. Pencil on paper. a4 Transformation. Portrait of a daughter. 2020. Pencil on paper. a4 Transformation. Portrait of a daughter. 2020. Pencil on paper. a4 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Model</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/journal/post-2020-03-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/journal/post-2020-03-01/</guid>
      <description> Model 2020. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2020. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2020. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2020. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2020. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2020. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2020. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2020. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2020. Pencil on paper. a2 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Model</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/journal/post-2019-11-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/journal/post-2019-11-01/</guid>
      <description> Model 2019. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2019. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2019. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2019. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2019. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2019. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2019. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2019. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2019. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2019. Pencil on paper. a2 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Almo</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/journal/post-2019-05-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 18:28:35 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/journal/post-2019-05-10/</guid>
      <description> Almo 2019. Pencil on paper. a3 Almo 2019. Pencil on paper. a3 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Model</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/journal/post-2018-12-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 18:28:35 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/journal/post-2018-12-10/</guid>
      <description>Model 2018. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2018. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2018. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2018. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2018. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2018. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2018. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2018. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2018. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2018. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2018. Pencil on paper. a2 Model 2018. Pencil on paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christina</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/journal/post-2014-12-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 18:28:35 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/journal/post-2014-12-01/</guid>
      <description> Christina 2014. Pencil on paper. a3 Christina 2014. Pencil on paper. a3 Christina 2014. Pencil on paper. a3 Christina 2014. Pencil on paper. a3 Christina 2014. Pencil on paper. a3 Christina 2014. Pencil on paper. a3 Christina 2014. Pencil on paper. a3 Christina 2014. Pencil on paper. a3 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ammersee in July</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/journal/post-2014-06-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 18:28:35 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/journal/post-2014-06-10/</guid>
      <description> Ammersee in July 2014. Pencil on paper. 13x18 Ammersee in July 2014. Pencil on paper. 13x18 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old time studies</title>
      <link>https://www.marinart.de/journal/post-2013-04-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 18:28:35 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.marinart.de/journal/post-2013-04-10/</guid>
      <description> Old man, study 1992. Pencil on paper. a2 Old man, study 1992. Pencil on paper. a2 Old man, study 1992. Oil on canvas. 40x40 Old man, study 1992. Oil on canvas. 40x40 Old man, study 1992. Pencil on paper. 60x80 Old man, study 1992. Pencil on paper. 60x80 Old women, study 2013. Pencil on paper. a2 Old women, study 2013. Pencil on paper. a2 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
